A nontechnical user starts with one simple sentence.
The IDE agent reads the repository rules, checks UiPath readiness, and registers a live governance gate.
No project work starts until a real UiPath Action Center approval exists.
Action Center hosts the explicit human approval task with a required approval checkbox.
The decision is submitted in UiPath. The agent does not trust a chat message as approval.
UiPath Data Fabric stores governance memory: CodeSoul, MinefieldHistory, Persona, and StateMemory.
The BPMN/agentic process canvas documents the orchestration design for the governed flow.
After API verification succeeds, Phase 0 begins with one plain-language question at a time.
The beginner answers practical business questions; the agent records each answer before continuing.
Phase 0 completes and creates a formal master plan before any raw code is written.
The repository contains the agent rules, UiPath connector, tests, and evidence for the governance flow.
Universal Agent OS: beginner idea, governed approval, auditable plan.